Guide to the Alumni Records Office, Yale University, Records of Alumni from the Classes of 1701-1978
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Forestry, Series XI
  - 1923 H-Z - 1925 A-S (Box 1204)
  - 1925 T-Z - 1927 A-K (Box 1205)
  - 1927 M-Z - 1928 (Box 1206)
  - 1929-1930 (Box 1207)
  - 1931-1932 (Box 1208)
  - 1933-1935 (Box 1209)
  - 1936-1938 (Box 1210)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 1211)
  - 1941-1946 (Box 1212)
  - 1947-1954 (Box 1213)
- Alumni from the Classes of 1871-1978, Accession 2000-A-047
  - Yale College, 1918-1941 (Box 1)
  - Yale College, 1942-1951 (Box 2)
  - Yale College, 1952-1959 (Box 3)
  - Sheffield and Engineering, 1927-1956 (Box 3)
  - Medicine, 1924-1954 (Box 3)
  - Medicine (Public Health), 1926-1954 (Box 4)
  - Law, 1917-1954 (Box 4)
  - Divinity, 1919-1954 (Box 5)
  - Graduate School, 1906-1934 (Box 5)
  - Graduate School, 1934-1953 (Box 6)
  - Graduate School, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Nursing, 1927-1954 (Box 7)
  - Honorary, 1871-1954 (Box 7)
  - Music, 1909-1954 (Box 7)
  - Drama, 1927-1949 (Box 7)
  - Drama, 1950-1978 (Box 8)
  - Art and Architecture, 1919-1954 (Box 8)
  - Forestry, 1924-1954 (Box 8)
- Alumni records for post-doctoral Classes of 1919-1953, 1914-1953; Accession 2001-A-022; 0.5; (1 box) (Box 1)
- Alumni records for students in World War II, circa 1939-1954; Accession 2001-A-156
  - A-F (Box 1)
  - G-O (Box 2)
  - P-Z (Box 3)
- Alumni death notices and obituaries for Yale College and Sheffield Scientific School Classes of 1909-1954, 1990-2006; Accession 2007-A-012
  - 1900-1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1921 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1922 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
  - 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9 - 10)
  - 1924 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
  - 1925 (Box 1, Folder 13 - 16)
  - 1926 (Box 2, Folder 17 - 19)
  - 1927 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 23)
  - 1928 (Box 2, Folder 24 - 29)
  - 1929 (Box 2, Folder 30 - 33)
  - 1930 (Box 3, Folder 34 - 37)
  - 1931 (Box 3, Folder 38 - 41)
  - 1932 (Box 3, Folder 42 - 47)
  - 1933 (Box 3, Folder 48 - 50)
  - 1933 (Box 4, Folder 51 - 53)
  - 1934 (Box 4, Folder 54 - 58)
  - 1935 (Box 4, Folder 59 - 64)
  - 1936 (Box 5, Folder 65 - 68)
  - 1937 (Box 5, Folder 69 - 72)
  - 1938 (Box 5, Folder 73 - 76)
  - 1939 (Box 5, Folder 77 - 79)
  - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 80 - 82)
  - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 83 - 84)
  - 1941 (Box 6, Folder 85 - 88)
  - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 89 - 92)
  - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 93 - 97)
  - 1944 (Box 6, Folder 98 - 101)
  - 1945 (Box 7, Folder 102 - 106)
  - 1945W (Box 7, Folder 107 - 111)
  - 1946 (Box 7, Folder 112 - 116)
  - 1947 (Box 7, Folder 117 - 118)
  - 1948 (Box 7, Folder 119 - 120)
  - 1948 (Box 8, Folder 121 - 124)
  - 1949 (Box 8, Folder 125 - 130)
  - 1950 (Box 8, Folder 131 - 135)
  - 1951 (Box 8, Folder 136 - 139)
  - 1952 (Box 9, Folder 140 - 141)
  - 1953 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - 1954 (Box 9, Folder 143)
- Alumni death notices and obituaries for the undergraduate and graduate Classes of 1909-1958, 1980-2005; Accession 2009-A-036
  The materials consist of alumni death notices, obituaries and general biographical information for Yale undergraduate and graduate members of the Classess 1909-1958 who died during the period 1980-2005.
  The materials are arranged chronologically by Class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Undergraduate Classes
    - 2000-2005 (Box 1)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 2)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 3)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 4)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 5)
    - 1943, 2000-2005 (Box 6)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 7)
    - 1945W-1947, 2000-2005 (Box 8)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 9)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 10)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 11)
  - Graduate Classes
    - 1980-2005 (Box 12)
    - 1980-2005 (Box 13)
    - 1980-2005 (Box 14)
    - 1980-2005 (Box 15)